# ADEPOJU SIJI SAMSON

Contact Address: L5/19, Kajola street, Amuda bus stop, along Ojoo express way, Ibadan Oyo State.

Telephone: 09062156016, 08154511767

Email: sijisamson1@gmail.com

# PERSONAL DATA

Date of birth: 14th November, 1991

Gender: Male

Marital status: Single

Nationality: Nigerian

State of origin: Osun

Local Govt of origin: Obokun

## PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am a team player with excellent communication skills and bag of enthusiasm. I am a seasoned examiner with over three years of marking experience. I possess the desire to succeed on any given task, I am persuasive and able to maximize effort towards generatingnew methods of impacting knowledge through successful development and implementation of well researched teaching initiatives. I am calm and able to get along with work colleagues and senior managers.

# EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS WITH DATE

M.A in view

Linguistics and Communication Studies (B.A)

Osun State University, Osogbo 2015

Senior School Certificate Examination (NECO/WAEC)

L.A Secondary Grammar School, Ibokun, Osun State. 2009

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Krystal Edge College, Akobo, Ibadan (2018 till present)

Freelance Journalist with Daily Trust Newspaper, NUJ Corespondence Chapel, Osogbo. (2017-2018)

Tutor with Dominion Achiever Pre-versity Bodija, Ibadan (2016-2017)

CEFN Secondary School, Anyigba, Kogi State (December 2015 - November 2016)

NUJ Correspondent Chapel, Osogbo (SIWES. June 2014 – November 2015)

#### SKILLS AND ABILITIES

Microsoft office, good interpersonal skills, ability to work effectively in a team, integrity and honesty, excellent oral and written communication skills, self motivated and target oriented.

#### **CAREER STATEMENT**

I feel that my three greatest strengths are firstly my ability to have a clear understanding of the learners needs. Secondly the satisfaction I get from being involved in interpersonal discussion, and my passion to influence the younger generation.

## LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

English and Yoruba

## **HOBBIES**

Driving, travelling and Interpersonal discussion

# REFREE (S)

Available on request